# Daniel Tan Nguyen

Earned 4-year degree in Software Engineering. Supportive and enthusiastic team player who is eager to work with passionate team of engineers and developers. Seeking a Software Engineer role in order to collaborate and assist in the software process.

(408) 667-1910

San Jose, CA

Danieltn91@gmail.com

www.danielnguyen.xyz

www.github.com/codeskiller

www.linkedin.com/in/danieltn

## **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

C#,.Net, Visual Basic, JavaScript, MySQL, Window Studio, SAP, MS Offices, Git, Sublime Text 3, XCode, Eclipse, Adobe Photoshop, Slack, Google services, Window OS, and Mac OS.

### **EXPERIENCE**

Final Test Technicain - 5/21/2018 - Present

Varian Medical Systems

- Follow process and produce quality machine.
- Repair/reject, report defective materials.
- Perform system and assembly level testing

Developer - 5/21/2018 - Present

Side Project - Varian Medical Systems

Progress Report - Visual Basic, C#, .Net on Window

- Maintain and develop reports.
- Analysis and troubleshoot any issue-bug.

- · Document systems test results
- Maintain compliance with all policies and procedures
- Work independently on Microsoft technologies.
- Build features per manager's requests.

#### **EDUCATION**

Bachelor of Science degree in Software Engineering - 08/2014 - 12/2017

San Jose State University, San Jose, CA

Relevant Coursework

- Web Programming
- Mobile Development
- Database Management
- Software Quality Testing
- Data Structures
- Java Programming
- Design Patterns
- Software Project Management
- Object-Oriented Design
- Information Security
- Software Process
- Human Computer Interaction

#### **SCHOOL PROJECT**

**DroneltOut – Swift, MapKit SpeechKit, Nuance** 02/2017-12/2017

- Researched and implemented scalable for voice control, predefined paths, and flying patterns for the drone.
- Collaborated closely with team members to plan, design, and develop robust solutions.
- Evaluated interface between hardware and software.
- Consulted regularly with professor on project status and technical issues.

#### **HIGHLIGHTS**

Problem-solving, Eager to learn, Self-motivated, Determine, Persistent, Responsibility, Project Management, Independent/teamwork.